ultimatemotorcycling.com 2018-10-30

# Legal Notice and Privacy Policy - Ultimate Motorcycling

_All content on this website, including articles, press releases and product information updates is for informational purposes only. This information should not be considered complete, up to date, and is not intended to be used in place of a visit, consultation, or advice of a legal, medical, or any other professional.  
_

Your privacy is important to Ultimate MotorCycling. So we’ve developed a Privacy Policy that covers how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, and store your information. Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices and let us know if you have any questions.

**Collection and Use of Personal Information**

Personal information is data that can be used to uniquely identify or contact a single person.

You may be asked to provide your personal information anytime you are in contact with Ultimate MotorCycling or an Ultimate MotorCycling affiliated company. Ultimate MotorCycling and its affiliates may share this personal information with each other and use it consistent with this Privacy Policy. They may also combine it with other information to provide and improve our products, services, content, and advertising.

Here are some examples of the types of personal information Ultimate MotorCycling may collect and how we may use it.

**What personal information we collect:**

When you create an Ultimate MotorCycling ID or participate in an online survey, we may collect a variety of information, including your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and contact preferences.

**How we use your personal information:**

The personal information we collect allows us to keep you posted on Ultimate MotorCycling’s latest announcements and upcoming events. It also helps us to improve our services, content, and advertising. If you don’t want to be on our mailing list, you can opt out anytime.

We also use personal information to help us develop, deliver, and improve our products, services, content, and advertising.

From time to time, we may use your personal information to send important notices, such as communications about purchases and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies. Although this information is important to your interaction with Ultimate MotorCycling, you may opt out of receiving these communications at any time.

We may also use personal information for internal purposes such as auditing, data analysis, and research to improve Ultimate MotorCycling’s products, services, and customer communications.

If you enter into a sweepstakes, contest, or similar promotion we may use the information you provide to administer those programs.

**Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information**

We also collect non-personal information − data in a form that does not permit direct association with any specific individual. We may collect, use, transfer, and disclose non-personal information for any purpose. The following are some examples of non-personal information that we collect and how we may use it:

We may collect information such as occupation, language, zip code, area code, unique device identifier, location, and the time zone where an Ultimate MotorCycling product is used so that we can better understand customer behavior and improve our products, services, and advertising.

If we do combine non-personal information with personal information the combined information will be treated as personal information for as long as it remains combined.

**Cookies and Other Technologies**

Ultimate MotorCycling’s website, online services, interactive applications, email messages, and advertisements may use “cookies” and other technologies such as pixel tags and web beacons. These technologies help us better understand user behavior, tell us which parts of our website people have visited, and facilitate and measure the effectiveness of advertisements and web searches. We treat information collected by cookies and other technologies as non-personal information. However, to the extent that Internet Protocol (IP) addresses or similar identifiers are considered personal information by local law, we also treat these identifiers as personal information. Similarly, to the extent that non-personal information is combined with personal information, we treat the combined information as personal information for the purposes of this

### Privacy Policy

Ultimate MotorCycling and its partners use cookies and other technologies in mobile advertising services to control the number of times you see a given ad, deliver ads that relate to your interests, and measure the effectiveness of ad campaigns. If you do not want to receive ads with this level of relevance on your mobile device, you can opt out. You will continue to receive the same number of mobile ads, but they may be less relevant because they will not be based on your interests. You may still see ads related to the content on a web page or in an application or based on other non-personal information. This opt-out applies only to Ultimate MotorCycling advertising services and does not affect interest-based advertising from other advertising networks.

Ultimate MotorCycling and our partners also use cookies and other technologies to remember personal information when you use our website, online services, and applications. Our goal in these cases is to make your experience with Ultimate MotorCycling more convenient and personal.

Knowing your country and language helps us provide a customized and more useful experience. If you want to disable cookies on your mobile device, go to Settings and then to the Cookies section.

For browsers, check with your provider to find out how to disable cookies. Please note that certain features of the Ultimate MotorCycling website may not be available once cookies are disabled

As is true of most websites, we gather some information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type and language, Internet service provider (ISP), referring and exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information to understand and analyze trends, to administer the site, to learn about user behavior on the site, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Ultimate MotorCycling may use this information in our marketing and advertising services.

In some of our email messages, we use a “click-through URL” linked to content on the Ultimate MotorCycling website. When customers click one of these URLs, they pass through a separate web server before arriving at the destination page on our website. We track this click-through data to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked in this way, you should not click text or graphic links in the email messages.

Pixel tags enable us to send email messages in a format customers can read, and they tell us whether mail has been opened. We may use this information to reduce or eliminate messages sent to customers.

**Disclosure to Third Parties**

Personal information will only be shared by Ultimate MotorCycling to provide or improve our products, services and advertising; it will not be sold or shared with third parties for their marketing purposes.

**Others**

It may be necessary − by law, legal process, litigation, and/or requests from public and governmental authorities within or outside your country of residence − for Ultimate MotorCycling to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for purposes of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary or appropriate.

We may also disclose information about you if we determine that disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our terms and conditions or protect our operations or users. Additionally, in the event of a reorganization, merger, or sale we may transfer any and all personal information we collect to the relevant third party.

**Protection of Personal Information**

Ultimate MotorCycling takes precautions — including administrative, technical, and physical measures — to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

When you use some Ultimate MotorCycling products, services, or applications or post on an Ultimate MotorCycling forum or social networking service, the personal information you share is visible to other users and can be read, collected, or used by them. You are responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in these instances. For example, if you list your name and email address in a forum posting, that information is public. Please take care when using these features.

**Access to Personal Information**

For personal information, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access so you can request that we correct the data if it is inaccurate or delete the data if Ultimate MotorCycling is not required to retain it by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, are extremely impractical, or for which access is not otherwise required by local law.

**Children**

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we learn that we have collected the personal information of a child under 13 we will take steps to delete the information as soon as possible.

**Third-Party Sites and Services**

Ultimate MotorCycling websites, products, applications, and services may contain links to third-party websites, products, and services. Information collected by third parties is governed by their privacy practices and we encourage you to learn about the privacy practices of those third parties.

**International Users**

Information you provide may be transferred or accessed by entities around the world as described in this Privacy Policy. Ultimate MotorCycling abides by the “safe harbor” framework set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information collected by organizations in the European Economic Area and Switzerland. Learn more about the U.S. Department of Commerce Safe Harbor Program.

**Our Company-wide Commitment to Your Privacy**

To make sure your personal information is secure, we communicate our privacy and security guidelines to Ultimate MotorCycling employees and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the company.

**Privacy Questions**

If you have any questions or concerns about Ultimate MotorCycling’s Privacy Policy or data processing, please contact us.

Ultimate MotorCycling may update its Privacy Policy from time to time. When we change the policy in a material way, a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated Privacy Policy.

Ultimate MotorCycling, LLC. 887 Patriot Drive, Unit B, Moorpark, CA 93021
